indiaprwire.com 2007-06-18

# Privacy Policy - IndiaPRwire.com

## Privacy Policy

**Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.**

Visitors to India PRwire.com website, subscribers to our newsletters, and clients and prospective clients of our service (collectively referred to as a "User" or "Users"), we log standard technical information such as your IP address. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our service, and to administer our Website. 

India PRwire.com uses cookies to keep track of your account. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to you.

India PRwire requires registration for certain services, such as the distribution of press releases, and our website may contain order forms for other products and services or online surveys. In order to provide services to you, we may ask for contact information (like name and email address), financial information (like account and/or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code and age). 

If you decide to submit a press release for distribution through our system we will transmit your entire press release, including any personal information therein contained, to our media contacts and online distribution points including search engines. Your submission of press releases through our system indicates consent with this policy. 

We may use your contact information to send you information about our company or our advertisers. We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, to deliver content that we think might be of interest to you, and to display the content according to your preferences. 

India PRwire may also disclose your personal information, the contents of your communications, and/or your contact and financial information, if required to do so by law, or with your consent, or in good faith/belief that such action is necessary: 

It is possible that as we continue to develop our business, India PRwire might be acquired. In such a transaction, your information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.

On occasion we may send you an email with an offering that is of general interest to the public relations community. Such offerings, when they occur, help us to continue providing this service.

This site contains links to other sites. India PRwire is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

We use a third party advertisement company to display advertisements on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Website, the third party ad company collects cookies received with banner ads, and we do not have access to this information. This Privacy Statement does not cover the privacy practices of companies who provide services or ads through our site. Please contact those companies directly for more information about their privacy practices.

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control, but we cannot guarantee complete security. 

Clients who have registered in order to use our services can change or update their account information and preferences by emailing Client Services at [contact@indiaprwire.com](mailto:contact@indiaprwire.com?subject=Contact%20IndiaPRwire.com "Contact IndiaPRwire.com").

From time to time we will email client prospects whom we have reason to believe might be interested in our services because of their involvement in the public relations, investor relations, or related fields. Prospects can opt-out of future communications simply by replying to the email and indicating their preference.

We provide subscribers to our email newsletters with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional communications at the point when we request your information. After they have signed up, subscribers can change their preferences regarding promotional communications, can subscribe to and/or unsubscribe from any of our email newsletters, and can modify other registration information previously provided to us by using the link provided at the bottom of any email newsletter we send to you.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back to our Website periodically.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of India PRwire, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us at the postal address or email address listed below. 

**India PRwire Pvt. Ltd**.  
A-14, Regency Park I  
DLF City, Phase - IV  
Gurgaon, Haryana  
India  
Pin: 122002  
Email: [contact@indiaprwire.com](mailto:contact@indiaprwire.com?subject=Contact%20IndiaPRwire.com "Contact IndiaPRwire.com")
